One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
That's why we gotta cast off - together, we can!
Sailing from sea to sea,
saying it's nothing but a fairy tale.
Truth is stranger than fiction, isn't it?
Don't pretend you can't see it.
Common sense is only what the majority says it is!
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
So let's go, Captain I'll-Do-It-My-Way!
Whaddya mean, "no can do"?
We haven't even started yet!
I wanna know it all! Now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can! This moment...
We can! I can! With this feeling of freedom...
Now... Now, oh yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
Tea Party Invitation
What?
Y-You've got to be kidding...
What the hell... Hey!
Where is everybody?!
What happened?! Grr! Who did this to Zou?!
Did the Straw Hats do this?!
What did they do to my home?!
This is a residential quarter where our ancestors used to live.
Zunesha has carried the whole history of the Mink Tribe without change.
One of the Mink Tribe's tradition that goes far back in that history is...
...exchanging clothes with foreigners, as a sign of friendship!
Oh, this is beautiful!
It's like a dress for somebody great.
Yes.
And that accessory is a national treasure.
What?! Are you giving it to me?!
Of course. Everyone agreed we should.
Garchu! Garchu-chu!
Mademoiselle, garchu.
Garchu.
How are you?! Garchu.
Tristan-chan!
Garchu!
Sanji-san, you sure like to greet everyone.
What is "garchu"?
Is it a miraculous magic word or something?
Sanji! It's from us to you, our great savior; Garchu!
Shut up! I don't want it from guys!
Oh, Sanji-san. Garchu!
Oh, boy! Viva minkship!
Is that a goddess?!
No...
Nami-san!
Garchu!
Where is Momo?
He's still locked in his room.
He feels more comfortable that way.
Plus, he shouldn't let them see his human form.
You're right.
We'd better not mention the word "samurai" while we're in this country.
Just give that annoying brat to the Minks
and let's leave this crappy island already!
Shut up!
Hey, Caesar, did you make the drugs?
I met my quota because I'm a genius.
Make more! Don't stop!
There are still so many injured people!
Keep working!
Why should I do such a thing...
Dr. Caesar, I came to pick up the drugs.
Hey, you're mistaken!
I'm Cedar the pharmacist!
Here.
Damn! Why am I making drugs to save people?!
Thank you, Dr. Caesar!
It's Cedar!
Man! This work disgraces my name, Caesar the genius mad scientist!
Oh yeah...
It's Cedar!
Baron Corpse,
your fans are waiting for you outside.
Erk!
I don't need popularity among dogs...
Pekoms!
It's you, Pekoms!
You're home!
Pekoms!
So you guys are all okay!
Dad! Mom!
All my relatives and friends!
Welcome home!
How long has it been?!
This brings back memories!
Yeah! You're looking good and I'm so happy!
Garchu!
You idiot! You're covered with cuts and bruises!
Don't tell me you're happy!
When I saw the city, I thought my heart would stop!
Garchu!
Hey!
You're hurting me!
It's all thanks to the Straw Hats!
If it weren't for their desperate rescue, I don't know what would've happened to us by now.
Really, thank you for staying alive!
Whoa-whoa, stop crying.
Damn!
I can't forgive Jack of the Beast Pirates!
How dare he do that to my home!
Look! Those guys from the Big Mom Pirates! They made it this far!
That's Pekoms! He came home.
He used to be an infamous delinquent.
Oh, so he's a Mink.
They must've heard this is where we were heading!
They want me!
Hey, please!
Don't hand me over to them.
You were our trump card against Doflamingo.
Now that Luffy and the others took him down, we don't care what happens to you.
Don't say such a thing! We're friends!
When did we become friends?!
You were whining about something at Dressrosa too. What did you do to Big Mom?
Oh, that's it! Hear me out!
I got an offer to research something which I haven't succeeded at yet,
and I lied to her and ripped her off pretty badly!
I had Doflamingo at my back so I pushed my luck!
So you asked for it.
I hope all they want is Caesar...
What?!
I'll kick your ass all over the New World...
...and make Fishman Island my territory!
Luffy picked a fight with Big Mom at Fishman Island.
We broke their ship too.
Hey, Black-Foot. Do you wanna work together with me and take them out?
Think about it!
Nami-san, stay with the rest here.
Okay.
Brook, come with me.
Hey, Black-Foot!
What about my cool idea to assassinate them?!
Idiots who can't think should shut up.
What do you Big Mom Pirates want?
Don't cause trouble.
The people in this country are hurt inside and out now.
We're not gonna run or hide.
All I can say is thank you! Grr!
H-Hey...
I didn't expect to see my home country devastated like this...
But you guys saved the people, didn't you?!
I owe you greatly!
How can I thank you...?
By Mama's order, we have business other than capturing Caesar.
It could spell doom for your pirate group.
Doom?
So let's forget it! The mission failed!
Just give us Caesar!
I'll just tell Mom that we let the Straw Hats get away!
Pekoms! Are you losing your mind?!
Put your feelings aside!
Shut up, newbie! I'll take the punishment!
They saved my family members and friends.
I can't do anything to them...
You coward!
You bastard!
He shot his ally in the back!
How could he do that?!
What did I just see?
He may not look like it but he's quite a well-known pirate.
However, when he chose to act on his pathetic feelings, he turned into such a coward.
There's no longer any use for him.
I'll do it myself!
Alright, guys! Come on out!
Go!
What?!
What?! Humans?!
What the hell?!
Give up! You're outnumbered!
Did the humans come out of his stomach?!
What kind of ability is that?!
I thought I saw humans in his hand but, that wasn't an illusion!
I ate the Castle Fruit and became a castle human.
I'm regarded in the same generation as your captain, so you know me, don't you?
Captain of the Firetank Pirates Capone "Gang" Bege Bounty: 300 million berry
When Luffy punched the Celestial Dragon at Sabaody, you were there, weren't you?!
We're not gonna make a scene here.
We don't want that, either.
If the Minks come, they'll definitely take your side.
I know how well they can fight.
Vito!
No! Let go of me!
Nami-san!
Chopper-san!
I-I'm sorry!
We couldn't help worrying so...
I'm sorry! I thought there were only two enemies!
Oh...
Caesar! Why don't you come out, too?!
We'll fire shotguns containing Sea Prism Stone towards the sky in two seconds!
Two!
One!
Wait a sec! I'm here! Don't shoot!
Don't point them at me!
Come to think of it, we don't have any bullets containing Sea Prism Stone.
What?!
But we have a spear that works like that!
Rather than standing around here talking, get into my castle.
That's an order!
Damn! He's completely in control.
Thank you for waiting.
Would you guys like to eat something?
No thanks.
You don't have to be humble.
Maybe a glass of wine?
We don't want anything!
Get down to business already!
He'll kill us! He'll kill us! He'll kill us!
You should cut yourself some slack sometimes.
We exchanged gunfire at sea a week ago, but the situation has changed since then.
I was asked to hand you this invitation.
It's an invitation to Mama's tea party.
Cut the crap.
Why would I wanna go to Big Mom's tea party?
The highlight of the party will be a wedding ceremony.
The groom is the third son of the Vinsmoke Family...
Groom Third son of the Vinsmoke family Sanji
Sanji!
What?!
What?!!
Groom Third son of the Vinsmoke family Sanji
The bride is the 35th daughter of the Charlotte Family,
Bride 35th daughter of the Charlotte family Pudding
The bride is the 35th daughter of the Charlotte Family, Pudding.
TEA PARTY
D-During a tea party...
Groom Third son of the Vinsmoke family Sanji
Bride 35th daughter of the Charlotte family Pudding
They'll hold Sanji's wedding?!
Groom Third son of the Vinsmoke family Sanji
Bride 35th daughter of the Charlotte family Pudding
Take it.
Groom Third son of the Vinsmoke family Sanji
Bride 35th daughter of the Charlotte family Pudding
TEA PARTY
Why, after all these years?!
Third son of the Vinsmoke family
I don't know the deal with your family!
You bastard! Are you trying to set fire to my castle?!
Hey, Sanji-kun, what is this all about?!
Are you gonna get married?!
Who made the decision without asking?!
Your family, of course!
Being a son of the Vinsmoke family means you're quite ill-bred.
V-V-Vinsmoke is Sanji-san's surname?!
The name gives me chills down my spine.
But no, that's not possible.
Hey, bring me a glass of wine!
Yes, sir!
Sanji-kun's family...
Oh!
"Noland the Liar"?
You know it, Sanji-kun?
But it says it was published in the North Blue.
Yeah. I was born in the North Blue.
Haven't I told you guys?
That's news. I thought you were from the East, too.
I grew up there. Well, who cares.
I remember feeling strange at that time.
We met him in the East Blue
but he said he was born in the North Blue.
What?! Are you sure, Nami-san?!
If that's true, it's a big deal!
In order to move to the East Blue from the North Blue, you have to surmount the Red Line!
That's right!
Is it difficult?
Yes, it's not just one family moving to another place!
It's a great voyage!
What kind of childhood did Sanji-san have?
And, you know,
Charlotte is Big Mom's surname!
What?!
That fool! Is he gonna marry Big Mom's daughter?!
Will he join an Emperor's family?!
If your fellow crewmember becomes her son-in-law, you guys will practically be her subordinates!
What?!
Don't jump to conclusions!
I'm under no obligation to go to such a tea party!
How ridiculous!
My wedding ceremony?
Marrying a woman I don't even know?!
You've got to be kidding me!
I don't want the Straw Hats to become your subordinates either!
Our captain isn't the type of guy who works under someone!
Luffy will...
...become the King of the Pirates!
Are we done here? You can have Caesar.
What?!
I think you have the wrong idea.
The invitation was only for you to see.
I wasn't looking for your answer.
You're in my body!
You guys have already been captured!
I'll take you all to Mama!
What?!
I'm sure you don't feel any motion...
but I'm already on the move.
Is it really moving?!
No! She'll kill me! Let me out!
You...
If you wanna fight, I'll fight you.
What the...!
Sanji-kun!
I have full command over the interior of the castle!
Everything is under my control!
Help!
Nami's sinking!
Nami-san!
Stop it!
I said stop it!
Are you alright?
Uh-huh.
What a relief!
Even if I don't rough you up,
you won't get away from Mama's tea party.
That's common knowledge throughout the New World.
That's right. Mama hates bitter sweets and empty seats at tea parties-rero.
When someone refuses her because he's ignorant-rero,
he'll cry in regret later
Advisor of the Firetank Pirates
"Phantom Gun" Vito
and I can't bear to see that-rero!
When you get an invitation to a tea party from Big Mom-rero,
that's basically an undeclinable summons!
Even the devil himself comes from hell to attend Mama's tea party, they say!
Of course, you have a choice not to go-rero.
But if you refuse...
Listen to me-rero.
How did you find that out?
That's a silly question.
Who do you think our master is?
The Four Emperors are the most powerful pirates there are, reigning supreme over the New World,
one of them being Big Mom herself.
She has it all.
If she tells someone she'll kill him, he'll die.
She doesn't bluff.
Stake your life on every word you say.
If you wish to stay alive without becoming anybody's subordinate,
do as she says, at least for now.
Sanji-san! Are you okay?
What did he say to you earlier?
What's the matter, Sanji?!
We'll fight even against an Emperor!
Be quiet!
Give me some paper and a pen.
Are you gonna leave a note for Straw Hat?
Hand this to Luffy and everybody.
Sanji-kun...
Nami-san.
Chopper.
Brook.
Believe this if nothing else.
I didn't mean to hide anything from my friends.
That's something from the past
that I thought I'd never have to deal with again.
I really need to go and sort things out!
Wait a minute, Sanji-san.
Do you mean "by yourself"?
I feel a powerful presence outside.
It's probably one of the Minks.
Are you ready?
Ready?
Good luck!
What about me?!
That fool!
He freed his allies!
That bastard!
Don't move, you bastards!
Why...?
Okay, listen carefully!
I bet you don't want me to blow your precious genius scientist's brains out!
I'll get even with you, Black-Foot!
I thought so.
You fools can't kill me either, can you?!
Hearing about this marriage solves a mystery for me.
My wanted poster says "Only alive"!
You gotta catch me alive!
If you kill me, you'd piss somebody off,
wouldn't you?!
Have you been told to treat me civilly without even cuffs?!
The person who made them write that phrase on the poster and the one who arranged my marriage
must be the same person!
Damn! Let's get out and chase them!
I said not to move!
Please don't move!
You know someone's got my back now, don't you?!
Don't worry! I'll come with you.
To sort things out with that person!
So don't do anything to my friends!
All of you, stay where you are!
What?!
Father!
There is a... monster... outside now!
Master Nekomamushi...
Cat monster!
I didn't know there was such a terrible thing here!
Hey!
You-gara, who are you?
I saw Pekoms lying down back there bleeding.
No, you got it wrong! I'm his crewmate!
Crewmate?
Yes, we belong to the same pirate group!
We've actually been attacked by the remnants of Jack's crew!
That's not true!
Why would I shoot my ally?!
Sanji-kun, come on out!
Why do you wanna stay?!
Tell us what's really going on, Sanji!
What do you mean you need to go?!
Why can't we all go together?!
Let's wait for Luffy-san and everybody,
Sanji-san!
This is my problem.
I'll be back.
Tell them "Hi" for me.
Castle Tank!
Sanji!
Sanji-kun!
Nami! Chopper! Should I just chase him?!
No, it's no use, Wanda-san!
Baron Corpse!
Even if we can catch up to him,
he has...
...no intentions of coming back now!
To my buddies,
I'm off to see a woman.
I'll be back.
Sanji